{
    "id": "af5be01d625d48bcb90274b73093d7e8",
    "title": "Good and well",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f9c93bdb390b4afa9c0482a33465b55b",
            "title": "Good And Well",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "That was a ………………….. movie.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The steak smells ……………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is doing ……………… in his studies.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The proposal sounds ……………….. to me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That necklace looks …………………. on you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t have a ……………… opinion about him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She speaks English very …………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The performance was remarkably ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She performed remarkably ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She gave me some ……………….. advice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}